===============OP=================
===============ED=================
CODE GEASS
- Lelouch of the Rebellion -
R2
BRITANNIAN RESIDENTIAL ZONE
TOKYO SETTLEMENT
This is 2-D-4. We are now entering
Tokyo Settlement-controlled airspace.
こちら2D4　まもなくトウキョウ租界管轄空域に入ります
Roger that. Your flight objective here
is commercial advertising, correct?
了解　飛行目的は広報宣伝で間違いないな
No change in that. As reported,
our flight duration will be for 14 hours.
変更なし
滞空時間も申告どおり　14時間を予定
確認した　上空飛行を許可する
That's confirmed.
You are cleared for overflight.
Acknowledged. I appreciate it.
対応　感謝します
We're all that are left now. All that's left of
the Black Knights who, along with Zero,
かつて　ゼロと共にブリタニアを恐怖させた　黒の騎士団も
once struck terror in the heart of Britannia.
もはや　我々を残すのみ
Still, it's too soon to give in to despair!
しかし　絶望にはまだ早い
If Operation Hien 4 is successful, then!
この「飛燕4号」作戦さえ成功すれば…
Yeah.
はい
Everyone... Forgive me.
みんな　すまん
Long live Japan!
日本　万歳
Lelouch.
ルルーシュ
Oh? Again? Persistent, aren't you?
またですか　しつこいですね
You won't get away this time!
もう逃がさないぞ　あ
Hey! About that thing!
よぉ　この前の…
ごめん　今度な
Sorry! Next time!
Lelouch, wait!
待て　ルルーシュ
Vice Prez!
副会長
Don't let her get you!
頑張って
Sure! Sure!
はいはい
You lost the moment you turned this
into a contest of physical strength.
体力勝負に持ち込んだ時点で　お前の負けだ
Aren't you going a little overboard? This is
just about a supplementary phys-ed class.
大袈裟過ぎませんか
高が体育の補修に
Then you should come to class in the first place!
だったらちゃんと授業に出ろ
I have enough school credit as it is, don't I?
単位は問題ないはずですよ
It's just colored smoke!
ただの着色ガスですから
Wait!
待て
Hang in there, Vice Prez!
頑張れ　副会長
Yeah! Thanks!
ああ　どうも
What kind of student
council president are you?!
お前　それでも生徒会長か
Oh, so sorry. I wasn't thinking.
あ　すいません　思わず…
LELOUCH!
ルルーシュ
You trying to kill me, Coach?
ぐぁ　殺す気ですか　先生
Rivalz?! When did you?!
リヴァル　いつの間に…
See you, Rivalz!
I need to borrow your bike!
リヴァル　じゃ　これ借りるな
Lulu, are you at it again?
ルルったら　またぁ
Asa mo yoru mo koikogarete
Morning and night, I long for you
朝も夜も恋い焦がれて
星になるよ 君守る
hoshi ni naru yo kimi mamoru
I'll become a star and protect you
戦いは行方知らず
tatakai wa yukue shirazu
No matter where the battle may take me
ashita to kinou no kousaten de
At the intersection of tomorrow and yesterday
明日と昨日の交差点で
交わらない君と僕
majiwaranai kimi to boku
You and I can't be together
今行くよ 僕は流れ星
ima iku yo boku wa nagareboshi
I'm a shooting star, on my way right now
sekai ga kuchihatetemo
Even if the world crumbles apart
世界が朽ち果てても 変わることの無いものがある
kawaru koto no nai mono ga aru
There are things which will never change
namida wo koraete demo
Even as we bear tears in our eyes
涙を堪えてでも 守るべきものが僕らにはある
mamorubeki mono ga bokura ni wa aru
There are things we must protect
nanman'nen nan'okunen mae kara no
A message that's been in my body
（nononono）
遅れまいと メッセージが絶えない
message ga tainai de
For thousands and millions of years,
（no）
uzukidasu... mayoi wa nai
Springs out... I have no reservations
剥き出す 撃ち抜く
（迷いは無い）
narihibiku... kantan da
Roars out... It's easy
（簡単だ）
shagareta koe de... asu wo yobu
In a hoarse voice... Calling tomorrow
しゃがれた声で 傷だらけの手で 君守る
kizudarake no te de... kimi mamoru
With my wounded hands... I protect you
way got you could like
I continue to fight...
I continue to fight!
朝も夜も恋い焦がれて
asa mo yoru mo koikogarete
Morning and night, I long for you
hoshi ni naru yo kimi mamoru
I'll become a star and protect you
星になるよ 君守る
戦いは行方知らず
tatakai wa yukue shirazu
No matter where the battle may take me
ashita to kinou no kousaten de
At the intersection of tomorrow and yesterday
明日と昨日の交差点で
交わらない君と僕
majiwaranai kimi to boku
You and I can't be together
宿命を切り裂く流れ星
sadame wo kirisaku nagareboshi
I'm a shooting star, tearing fate apart
afureru kimi no namida boku ga ima ubaisaru
I'll take away your overflowing tears right now
溢れる君の涙 僕が今奪い去る
THE DAY A DEMON AWAKENS
まったく　放課後ぐらい自由にさせてほしいよな
For crying out loud!
Can't they leave me alone after school?
でも　兄さんが授業　サボってばかりいるから
But they only do that because you
cut class all the time, big brother.
かったるいじゃないか　あんなの
Because I find them boring!
差入れ　会長から
Have some. The Prez gave it to me.
おいおい
Whoa! Whoa!
だって　兄さんが…
But big brother, you!
そうか　ごめん
Yeah, right. Sorry.
ゼロが起こした反乱事件
It's been a year since the Black
Rebellion, the revolt started by Zero.
「ブラックリベリオン」から　もうすぐ1年
このエリア11も　すっかり落ち着いた
Things have finally quieted down,
even here in Area 11.
事件当初はいろんな噂が飛び交って
When the incident began,
all sorts of rumors flew around.
俺たち兄弟も　ブリタニア本土に帰ろうかと思ったけど
At one point, I thought about going
back to the homeland with my brother.
進路調査表は出した
Did you submit your
career aptitude test yet?
Hm?
ヴィレッタ先生が怒ってたから
That's why Coach Villetta was so upset.
Oh.
大学に行くの
Going to university?
まだ決めてないんだよ
I haven't decided yet.
I'm sick of being a student.
学生って身分も飽きたし
とは言え　人に使われるってのもさ
Although I'm not ready to be
used by other people yet, either.
ふふっ　兄さんらしいよ
Typical answer.
でも無駄か
Even if I enter the business world,
what can I hope to accomplish?
社会に出ても　どうせ上には　大企業や貴族様たちが居座っている
I'll still have the big corporations
and the nobility above me.
完成された世界
A fixed world.
大人のヒエラルキーに組み込まれるだけさ
I'll just be absorbed into
the hierarchy of adults.
これはイレヴンに対する差別ではない　区別だ
This is not discrimination against Elevens.
It's differentiation!
イレヴンはゼロという詐欺師に踊らされ
The Elevens showed themselves to
be a dangerous, belligerent people...
日本人と言う名に戻ろうとした
who followed the swindler known as Zero and
took to calling themselves "Japanese" again!
好戦的で危険な人種である
故に我らブリタニアによって管理、教育されねばならない
And so we Britannians must
control and educate them!
イレヴンは負けた　力がなかったから
The Elevens lost.
They didn't have the strength.
大人しくしていれば
「矯正教育エリア」に格下げされることもなかったのに
If they'd just kept quiet,
this place wouldn't have been
downgraded to a re-education Area.
ゼロ　バカな男だ
Zero... He was a fool.
何をやっても　どうせ世界は…
No matter what you try, the world is...
お急ぎください　カナレス総督
Please hurry, Viceroy Calares. The delegation
from the Chinese Federation is waiting.
中華連邦の方々が…
分かっている
Understood. Anyway, what
about the O.S.I.'s operation?
それより　機情局の作戦は
（機情局：機密情報局）
はい　バベルタワーで
Yes, my lord. At Babel Tower.
よりによってこんな日に
On today of all days...
What could His Majesty be thinking?
皇帝陛下は何をお考えなのか
今更　黒の騎士団の残党に　何ができるとは思えぬが
I doubt the remnants of the Black Knights
can do anything to us at this point.
それにゼロはもう死んだのだからな
Besides, Zero is long since dead.
手を休めるな　イレヴンのサルが
Quit slacking off, you Eleven monkey!
Y-Yes, sir!
は　はい
対象が到着しました　想定通りです
Target is now arriving, as predicted.
B3より5thゲートに入ります
Now entering fifth gate from B-3.
今回こそ現れますかね
You think she'll show this time?
そうでなければ困る
I certainly hope so.
It's risky to let him leave the settlement.
租界外延部に出すというリスクまで負ったのだからな
まぁいいけどさ
Very well, then. I just wanted a ride
from you, but if you really want to...
本当は送ってくれるだけでよかったんだ
今日のは非合法だし
Today I'll be breaking the law.
補導じゃ済まないよ
If you get arrested,
it'll be serious.
警察なんか…
The cops don't scare me.
でもどうして
But why do this?
You don't even want money, do you?
兄さんお金が欲しいわけじゃないでしょう
決まってる
Need you ask? It's because I want
to battle even tougher opponents!
もっと強いやつと戦いたいからさ
嘘だ　こんなのただの退屈しのぎ
That's a lie. I do this out of boredom.
In short, I'm...
要するに　俺は…
さぁ　本日の注目の兄弟対決
And now, today's main event,
a match between brothers!
生き残るのは兄か弟か
Will the older brother survive,
or the younger one?
なんとこちらの試合　10ラウンド連当の方に　7ポイント…
Odds of the fight going ten rounds is seven coins.
兄さん　帰ろう　ここは…
Big brother, let's go. This place is...
いいじゃないか　分かりやすくて
A single round bet will pay off three coins!
見ろよ　笑って遊ぶのは俺たちブリタニア人
Observe. The ones laughing and
having fun are we Britannians.
笑われて働くのがイレヴン
The ones being laughed at
and working are the Elevens.
見ない振りをしたって　結局は…
You pretend not to notice, but in the end...
虽だからって…
Then why?
分かってる　でも事実だ
I know, but it's the truth.
イレヴンは二度負けたんだ　枢木首相の時と　ゼロの時
The Elevens lost twice. First with Prime
Minister Kururugi and again with Zero.
力もないくせに反乱なんか…
How could they rebel when
they don't have the strength?
I'm so sorry!
あ　申し訳ありません
いや…いいって
No, it's fine.
私はイレヴン
But, I'm an Eleven and
you're a Britannian student!
貴方はブリタニアの学生さんですから
なら　尚更だ
All the more reason.
You hate having your position...
嫌いなんだ　立場を振りかざすのは
held over you like a sword,
don't you?
でも　力のない人間は我慢しなくちゃいけないんです
Even so, the powerless have
no choice but to bear it.
たとえ相手が間違っていても
Even if their opponent is wrong.
君たちの価値観をオレに押し付けないで欲しいな
I'd appreciate it if you wouldn't
push your values on me.
I beg your pardon.
申し訳ありません
顔を見せてくれないか
Let me see your face. Hm?
Hmpf! Nice goods!
いい商品だ
本日のウサギ狩り　大猟で何よりでございます
We've got a large, quality catch
of bunnies today, sir!
私は売り物じゃない
I'm not for sale!
売り物だよ
Oh, yes you are.
Losers don't have any rights!
勝ち取らない者に権利などない
イレギュラー　トラブルが発生しました
Unplanned trouble occurring.
「力なき自らの生まれを悔やみたまえ」
Curse your own birth for not having power.
That's what His Majesty says, right?
皇帝陛下もおっしゃっているだろう
皇帝…
His Majesty...
弱肉強食　それが世界のルールだ
The strong eat the weak.
That's the rule of this world!
兄さん　マフィアだよ
Big brother, he's with the Mafia!
傲慢だな
How arrogant.
自分は「食べる側」にいるつもりか
Are you planning to devour her?
学生君　これが大人の世界だよ
Get lost, student.
This is the grownup world in here.
なら　大人の世界と学生
Well then, will the adult world
eat the student, or vice-versa?
どちらが「食べる側」か
とりあえず　これではっきりさせよう
Why don't we answer that with this?
チェスで
With chess?
兄さん　いけない
Big brother, don't!
もう遅い
Too late, right, guys?
な
学生は本当に何も知らない
Students really don't know
anything, do they?
That's not true, Mr. Black King.
そうでもないさ
黒のキングさん
こっちの世界では名の知れた打ち手なんだろう
You're a famous chess player
in this world, aren't you?
So, you knew who I was, did you?
ほぅ　知った上でかね
ゼロさえいれば　お前らなんかに…
If Zero was here, you wouldn't be so tough!
もう言うな　裏切り者のことは
Don't mention that traitor around me again.
Zero didn't betray us!
裏切ってなんかねぇよ　ゼロは
静かにしろ
Pipe down!
Okay! I hear you! I'm sorry!
分かった　ごめんなさい
何か事情があったんだろう
There must have been circumstances.
事情？
Circumstances?
What reason would make...
最終決戦で指揮官がいなくなる理由なんて
the commander vanish
during the decisive battle?!
やめろ
Stop it!
In the end, Zero is still dead!
いずれにせよ　ゼロは死んだのだ
死んだ？
Dead?
チェックメイト
Checkmate.
Im-Impossible!
バ　バカな
The student beat him!
学生が勝った
黒のキングが負けるなんて
The Black King lost!
How could King have lost so easily?
食べられるのはそちらでしたね
Looks like it was you who got eaten.
ふん　困ったね
Hm, how troublesome.
こんな噂が広まっては
I won't be able to show my face
if word of this gets around.
私の面子が立たぬ
言いふらすような趣味は
I don't care for spreading rumors.
違うよ学生君
No, Mr. Student, I mean how
they'll hear how you cheated me!
君が仕掛けたイカサマの話をしているんだ
イカサマ？
Cheated?!
いけない子供だ
What a naughty boy you are...
あ　待ってくれ
Wait, please!
チェスでイカサマなんて
Cheat at chess?!
出来る訳がない
There's no way to do that!
拘束しろ
Hold him. Now, to make some evidence...
さて　証拠を造ろうか
薄汚い大人が
You filthy adult!
正しいことに　価値はないんだよ
Playing fair doesn't win the game, kid!
兄さん…
Let him go!
テロか
Terrorists?!
Move out!
出撃
来て　こっち
Come on! This way!
What? Hey!
兄さん
Big brother!
An airship, eh? Their final gasp.
飛行船とはな　最後のあがきか
機密情報局　オペレーションバルハラ7号　開始
Office of Secret Intelligence,
initiate Operation Valhalla 7.
イエス　マイ　ロード
Yes, My Lord!
なんだ
What's this?! What's happening?!
何がおきている
何が
WHAT?!
ようこそ　エリアArea 11へ
Welcome to Area 11.
大層な出迎えですが
Such an impressive reception for us.
ゼロは死んだと聞いていましたが
Although I heard that Zero was dead now.
ゼロ　いえいえ
Zero? No, no.
中華連邦の方々に
我がブリタニアを理解して頂くには　話が早いかと思いまして
I thought the Chinese Federation would
understand us Britannians better this way.
存外直截的な手を
My... How unusually straightforward.
Hm?
お腰の物をこちらに
If we may please have the item on your hip.
治安は万全です　そのようなアンティークは…
Our security is perfect, sir.
You won't need an antique like that.
星刻　無礼であろう
Xing-ke, how rude of you!
Forgive me.
失礼しました
我ら中華連邦をご理解頂くには　話が早いかと思いまして
I thought your Britannians would understand
the Chinese Federation better this way.
Why, you...
この…
Wait, what about my bets?!
Gimme my winnings!
あれ
兄さん　こっち
Big brother, this way!
H- Hey!
No! Wait!
待って
何　目標を見失った？
What? We've lost sight of the target?!
はい　私たちも突入します
Right. We're going in, too.
Understood!
分かった
バベルタワーを襲撃したテロリストは　ナイトメアを数機保持している模様
The terrorists attacking Babel Tower appear
to be armed with several Knightmares.
作戦開始に伴い　周辺クリーニングは完了
Ready to commence operation.
Perimeter cleared.
よし　セブンス·シークエンスに入る
All right, enter seventh sequence.
Commander, Viceroy Calares is...
隊長　カラレス総督が…
地方の官吏など無視しろ
Ignore that local bureaucrat.
我々は皇帝陛下の命を受けているのだ
We're under orders of the emperor himself!
イエス　マイ　ロード
Yes, My Lord.
Let the Elevens use the stairs!
イレヴンは階段を使え
We're overloaded!
重量オーバーだ
Don't push!
テロリスト
Terrorists? What are remnants of
the Black Knights doing here?
黒の騎士団の残党が如何してこんなところに
ブリタニア軍だ
Britannian soldiers!
God damned Britannians!
ブリタニアが
ごめん　あたしがちゃんと捕まえなかったから
Sorry! I couldn't bring him
here like we planned!
気にするな　今卜部さんたちが捜している
Don't sweat it! Urabe and the others
are looking for him right now.
分かった
Gotcha!
GUR
GUREN MK-II STARTUP
ロロ　こっちだ
Rolo! This way!
どういうことだ
What's going on? That Knightmare
before! Was it... protecting me?
さっきのナイトメア
まさか　オレを…
兄さん　これから
Big brother, what'll we do?
安心しろ　絶対に逃げられる
Don't worry. We'll get out of
here, I promise. I'll get us out.
逃がしてやるから
そうだね　僕たちは
S-Sure. We will.
Rolo!
ロロ
兄さん
BIG BROTHER!
ルルったら　ロロまで悪事に引き込んで
Now Lulu's dragging Rolo
into his bad habits!
素直に言えば　ルルちゃんが心配だって
Why not just admit that you're
worried about your darling Lulu?
I am not!
違います
There she goes again.
またまた
もう
Jeez...
ロ　ロロ
R- Rolo?
ロロ
ROLO!
通じないか
I can't get through! Now what?
At this rate, we'll both be!
どうする
このままじゃオレたちは
いや　助けてみせる
No! I have to try and save him!
たった一人の弟を救う力ぐらいあるはずだ
I have to be able to save
my only brother, at least!
Even I must have that much strength!
オレにだって　それぐらいの力は…
オレにだって…
Even I!
テロリストの仕業
The terrorists did this?!
しかし　エレヴンまで
But... The Elevens were killed, too!
Are they still relying on Zero?
まだ　ゼロなんかにすがって
黒の騎士団
The Black Knights!
殺す気か　どうする　逃げたとしても…
Do they want to kill me?
What do I do?! Even if I run away...
Lelouch.
ルルーシュ
向かいに来た　ルルーシュ
I came for you, Lelouch.
私は味方だ
I'm on your side.
お前の敵はブリタニア
Your enemy is Britannia.
契約しただろう　私は共犯者
We have a contract.
We're both accomplices.
契約？共犯者？
Contract? Accomplices?
私だけが知っている　本当のお前を
Only I know. The real you.
本当の　オレ
The real me?
ルルーシュ…
Le... louch...
おい
H- Hey!
ブリタニア軍
Britannian soldiers?!
おい　待てよ　何が
W-Wait, what are you?
やめろ　まだ生きてる…
Stop it! She's still alive!
お役目ご苦労
You've served your purpose well,
Lelouch Lamperouge.
ルルーシュ·ランペルージ君
役目？何の話だ
Purpose?
What are you talking about?!
私たちはずっと観察していた
We've had our eye on you
for a long time now.
6時59分起床
6:59 AM - Awakens.
7:12 AM - Watches the news with his
little brother while eating breakfast.
7時12分より弟とニュースを見ながら朝食
視聴内容に思想的偏りは無し
No ideological deviations with what he sees.
8時54分登校
8:45 AM - Goes to school.
ホームルームと一時間目も授業は出席せず　屋上で読書
Cuts homeroom and first period class.
Instead, reads on the roof.
二時間目　物理の授業は…
Second hour, for his physics class...
今日のオレだ
That's... what I did today...
飼育日記と言うところかな
Perhaps you can call it
a breeding log. For our bait.
餌の
餌？
Bait?
罠と言ってもいい
Or call it a trap if you wish.
For that witch.
その魔女を　C.C.を誘い出すために
All to lure C.C. out of hiding!
待ってくれ　何を言ってるんだ
Wait, please!
What are you talking about?!
私は男爵だからね
I'm a baron, boy, and as such
I have no further words for my bait!
これ以上餌と話す気はない
さ　処分の時間だ
Now, time to dispose of you.
これで目撃者はいなくなる
There can't be any witnesses left.
処分？
Dispose?
オレらは　終わる？
Is this the end for me?
何も分からずに
Without knowing anything? So easily?
こんな簡単に？
ふざけるな
To hell with that!
Power! If I just had power!
力
力さえあれば
ここから抜け出す力
Power to get out of here!
Power to not lose to the world!
世界に負けない力が…
何なんだ　これは
What... What is this?
力が欲しいか
You desire power?
その声　さっきの…
That voice... The girl from before?
力なら　お前はもう持っている
You already possess
the power you seek.
忘却の折に閉じ込められているだけだ
It's just imprisoned
in a cage of amnesia.
思い出せ
Remember. Who you really are!
The power of the king!
本当のお前を
王の力を
今こそ封印を解き放つ
Let the seal now be broken!
そうか　オレの日常に棘のように突き刺さっていた苛立ち
I see now...
The irritation which pricked me
like thorns in my everyday life.
ああ　すべてが偽りの記憶
Yes... It was all phony memories.
思い出した
I remember now... I am!
オレは
I am!!!
オレがゼロだ！
I am... ZERO!
ルルーシュ　許しは乞わないよ
Lelouch, I won't ask for forgiveness.
We're friends, aren't we?
友達だろう…オレたちは
Yes...
That's your answer, isn't it, Suzaku?
ああ　それがお前の答えか　スザク
私を処分する前に　質問に答えてもらえたい
Before you dispose of me,
I'd like you to answer a question.
That girl's still alive!
あの女生きている
バカな
Impossible!
She was shot through the heart!
心臓を打ち抜いたのに
無力が悪だと言うのなら
If it's wrong to be powerless,
does having power make you right?
力は正義なのか
復讐はあくだろうか　友情は正義足り得るだろうか
Is vengeance wrong?
Is friendship right?
悪も正義もない
There is no right or wrong.
「餌」にはただ「死」という事実が残るのみだ
The only reality left for bait
is simply death.
そうか　ならば君達にも事実を残そう
I see. Then that reality is all
that is left for you as well.
ルルーシュ·ヴィ·ブリタニアが命じる
Lelouch vi Britannia commands you!
貴様たちは　死ね
All of you... DIE!
It... It can't be!
ま　まさか…
イエス　ユア　ハイネス
Yes, Your Highness!
あの日から　オレの心には納得がなかった
Ever since that day,
my heart just couldn't accept it.
かみ合わない　偽物の日常
This phony life I couldn't fit into.
The lost time.
ずれた時間
別の記憶を植えつけられた
These other memories planted within
me to give me a life as one of the herd.
家畜の人生
しかし　真実はオレを求め続けた
But the truth continues
to lead me to itself.
そう　間違っていたのはオレじゃない　世界の方だ
That's right! It wasn't me
who was wrong! It's the world!
世界は変わる　変えられる
The world will change.
I will change it!
お待ちしておりました　ゼロ様
Pardon the wait, Master Zero!
どうか　我らにご命令を
Please, give us your orders!
いいだろ
Very well! After all...
なぜならば　私はゼロ
I am Zero!
The man who will destroy the world!
世界を壊し
世界を創造する男だ
The man who will
create the world anew!
イエス　ユア　マジェスティ
Yes, Your Majesty.
誰にも譲るつもりはありません
I have no intention of
giving this job to anyone else.
ゼロを殺すのは　自分です
The one who will kill Zero... shall be me.
胸の中 いつか拾った
Mune no naka itsuka hirotta
Someday let's try to pick up and rebuild
幸せの欠片 集めてみよう
Shiawase no kakera atsumete miyou
The fragments of happiness in our hearts
忘れかけていたメロディー
Wasurekaketeita melody
That nearly forgotten melody
色褪せず僕の真ん中に
Iroasezu boku no man'naka ni
Stay vivid, deep inside of me
ありがとう 心から 僕に今があるのはみんなのおかげさ
Arigatou kokoro kara
I thank you from the bottom of my heart
Boku ni ima ga aru no wa minna no okagesa
Everything I have now, I owe to everyone
ありがとう 心から 次は僕がみんなにハッピー贈るよ
Arigatou kokoro kara
I thank you from the bottom of my heart
Tsugi wa boku ga minna ni happy okuru yo
Next I'll send happiness to everyone
何もかも忘れないよ あの日の僕も僕だから
Nanimokamo wasurenai yo
I won't forget anything
Ano hi no boku mo boku dakara
Because I'm still the same as I was that day
「大好きだよ」って　いつも言ってあげなきゃ駄目だね
Daisuki da yo'tte itsumo
You need me to keep on saying
Itte agenakya dame da ne
How much I love you
涙がこぼれそうな長い夜は ふっと振り返って
Namida ga kobore sou na nagai yoru wa
On those long nights, your tears about to overflow
Futto furikaette
Just turn around
足跡を辿るんだ あの日を忘れないように
Ashiato wo tadorun'da
Follow those footprints
Ano hi wo wasurenai you ni
So that you'll never forget that day
許せはしない　許してはいけない
I can't forgive them.
I mustn't forgive them!
オレの記憶はオレであるための真実だ
My memories are
my own reality!
償いのときは来た
ゼロが戻ってきたと言う事実の意味を
ブリタニアに思い出させてやる
My own personal truth!
There is someone who trampled them,
made me into his livestock.
もう　うその支配はいらないから
Who looked down on me
as mere bait for his trap!
The time for payback has come!
I'll make Britannia remember the true
meaning of Zero's return to this world.
Because I have no more
need for their phony rule.
PLAN FOR INDEPENDENT JAPAN